# Mahmoud ElHassan Mahmoud

51 Ibn Rahmon St, Hadra, Alexandria

🛮 +201005152604 | 💌 mahmoudelhassan9@gmail.com | 🖸 portfolio-mahmoudelhassan.vercel.app/ | 🛅 www.linkedin.com/in/mahmoud-elhassan-94r

#### Personal Profile

An ITI Institute graduate student enrolled in the track full-stack web development .Net and Angular. Dedicated to software engineering, having two or more years of expertise, and specializing in full-stack web development, and algorithms. Searching mainly for Back-end, Front-end, and Database.

### **Education**

M.K.S Language School,

Smouha, Alexandria, Egypt

High School

May 2013

Faculty of Tourism and Hotels at Alexandria University

Alexandria, Egypt June 2013 - June 2017

Bachelor in Hotels Management Department

Alexandria, Egypt

Information Technology Institute (ITI) Full Stack web development .Net and Angular

August 2022 - November 2022

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

**Hilton Green Plaza** 

Alexandria, Egypt

Front office Agent July 2017 - November 2019

**Americana Group KFC** 

Bahrain

Assistant Restaurant Manager

January 2020 - October 2021

Upwork, Kahmsat, Mostaqel

Online

Freelancer November 2022 - Till Now

#### Skills

Programming ASP.Net | ASP.Net core (C, JQuery, Ajax, Jason, etc.), HTML/CSS, JavaScript, SQL Server, Angular JS, and React JS

Miscellaneous

Microsoft Office, Firebase, and GitHub.

Soft Skills

Time Management, Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation, and Engaging Presentation.

### Courses\_\_\_\_\_

2022 Udacity, Web Development

2022 Mahara-Tech, Database Fundamentals

2022 Mahara-Tech, JavaScript

Mahara-Tech, Freelancing 2022

2020 Baharain, Yum Courses Online: Food Safety, Delivery, FOH, MOH, BOH, LAS

2016 Alexandria University, COMSYS Program

2015 Alexandria University, Awards HACCP Program

# **Languages**

**English** Professional proficiency Arabic Native proficiency

APRIL 2, 2023